Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 2 Locals, 2.
  - Local 202
    - Local 202 Outgoing Correspondence, June 12, 1941-March 2, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Ernest Stone to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Cimino Testimonial Dinner, October 29, 1945; 1.
      - Marie Sutton to Fitzgerald Regarding Women and Seniority, March 2, 1949; 2.
      - Charles V. Venzio to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 12, 1945; 3.
      - Local 202 to General Executive Board Regarding Matthew Campbell Death, June 12, 1941; 4.
    - Local 202 Salary and Expense Letters, April 2, 1941-January 9, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Karan, April 2, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Almeida, May 3, 1941-January 9, 1942; 2-10.
    - Local 202 Finances, May 4, 1941-December 6, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Bond Form, May 7, 1941; 1.
      - Paul Barletta to Julius Empsak, December 6, 1952; 2.
    - Local 202 Batchelder Reservations, November 3-4, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Edward Matthews Telegram to Prince George Hotel, November 3, 1943; 1.
      - Prince George Hotel to Matthews, November 4, 1943; 2.
    - Local 202 Insurance, May 15-22, 1046 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Arthur Batchelder to Julius Emspak, May 15, 1946; 1.
      - Empsak to Batchelder, May 16, 1946; 2.
      - Batchelder to Emspak, May 21, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak Secretary to Albert Olsen, May 22, 1946; 4.
    - Local 202 Elections, November 1946 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Local 202 Officers Letter to Paul Seymour, November 9, 1946; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald Telegram to Leo Benoit, November 12, 1946; 2.
      - Seymour and David Scribner Report, November 14, 1946; 3.
      - Telephone Discussion with Benoit, November 14, 1946; 4.
      - Conversation with Benoit, November 16, 1946; 5.
      - Resolution Regarding Local 202 Elections with November 27, 1946, Allan Haywood Letter to Fitzgerald, November 1946; 6.
    - Local 202 Factionalism, August-September 1948 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - "The Members Run This Union!" with August 5, 1948, Leo Benoit Letter to James Matles, August 1948; 1.
      - Telephone Call Digest with William Lieberman, September 17, 1948; 2.
    - Local 202 Per Capita Reports, September 26-October 27, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - Per Capita Report, September 26, 1950; 1.
      - Hugh Harley to Julius Emspak, October 24, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to Harley with Ray Memo to Paula, October 27, 1950; 3.
    - Local 202 Correspondence and Meeting Proceedings, February 6, 1942-July 22, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - W.G. Marshall to James Matles Regarding Westinghouse Contracts, February 6, 1942; 1.
      - Meeting Proceedings of Local 202 Representatives and Management Representatives, May 21, 1942; 2.
      - Army-Navy Excellence Award in Production, January 21, 1943; 3.
      - Richard Linsley to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Westinghouse Collective Bargaining, July 22, 1943; 4.
    - Local 202 Correspondence, War Labor Board Ruling and Resolution, 1944-1950 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - War Labor Board Ruling Regarding Wages and Tool Designer with May 30, 1944, Jack Simon Letter to Edward Matthews, May 1944; 1.
      - Mass Meeting Resolution Regarding Factionalism with March 1, 1949, Leo Benoit Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, February 20, 1949; 2.
      - Matthews Telephone Conversation Digest Regarding Factionalism, October 10, 1949; 3.
      - Hugh Harley to Matthews Regarding Address Change, 1950; 4.
      - Harley to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 1, 1950; 5.
      - Ray Memo to Kathleen Regarding Local 202 Officers, 6.
    - Local 202 Newspaper, The United Front, October 30, 1940-July 8, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Local 202 Newspaper, 202 Election Beacon, October 4, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Local 202 Newspaper, UE United Front, March 23, 1950-February 13, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Local 202 Pamphlet, Who Runs UE, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Local 202 Leaflets, 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - "It's No Secret" Regarding Factionalism, 1946; 1.
      - James Matles Open Letter to Local 202 Regarding Factionalism, June 24, 1948; 2.
      - "What About" Regarding Factionalism, 1949; 3.
      - "Thank You! Tony Cimino" Regarding Factionalism, 1949; 4.
    - Local 202 Newspaper Clippings, October 6, 1947-October 4, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - "UE Trying to Rule Locals White Charges," Springfield Union, October 6, 1947; 1.
      - "Big Gain for Anti-red Forces Seel in Results of Westinghouse Vote," Springfield Union, October 10, 1947; 2.
      - "Defense of UE Leaders Hit by Cimino," Springfield Union, October 18, 1947; 3.
      - "Sign Loyalty Affidavit", October 24, 1947; 4.
      - "National UE Leader Dodges Red Issue at Union Meeting Here!," Springfield Union, January 14, 1948; 5.
      - "Short Work Week Again Considered", June 12, 1948; 6.
      - "UE Leaftist Hotly Denies Commie Link," Daily News, June 18, 1948; 7.
      - "Matles Says General Electric Negotiations Ask 25 Cents Pay Cut," Springfield Republican, June 19, 1948; 8.
      - "Sign of Some Restlessness in UE Circles," Springfield Union, Augsut 26, 1948; 9.
      - "Lieberman: Why No Words Against Soviet in UE Paper", September 10, 1948; 10.
      - "Paran Assails Critics of US Politics," Springfield Republican, September 11, 1948; 11.
      - "They Don't Want Anything Red", September 12, 1948; 12.
      - "Tired of Criticism", September 13, 1948; 13.
      - "Westinghouse Union Leftist Opens Campaign," Springfield Union, September 27, 1948; 14.
      - "UE Members of Democratic Action Goals are Outlined by Chairman," Springfield Union, October 2, 1948; 15.
    - Local 202 Newspaper Clippings, October 15, 1948-April 29, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - "Westinghouse UE Leader Hits at Red Smear," Springfield Union, October 15, 1948; 1.
      - "Left Winger Defeat Encourages Union," Springfield Daily News, December 28, 1948; 2.
      - "Wallace Becker is Out as Head of Large Unit of UE," Springfield Union, December 28, 1948; 3.
      - "Cimino Claims UE Right-wrong Win No Up Set," Springfield Daily News, December 19, 1948; 4.
      - "Cimino Critical in Statement," Springfield Union, December 30, 1948; 5.
      - "Lieberman and Benoit are Defeated as of Today," Springfield Union, December 31, 1948; 6.
      - "UE Right Wing Policies Backed by Group Here", 1948; 7.
      - "Benoit Elected to Conference Board", February 22, 1949; 8.
      - "Mrs. Sutton Didn't Talk Married Women Issue at Mass Meeting", February 22, 1949; 9.
      - "Westinghouse UE Local Also Rejects Agent," Springfield Republican, February 22, 1949; 10.
      - "Death Blow to UE Left Wingers Believed Dealt," Springfield Union, February 22, 1949; 11.
      - "Commie Resolve Attracts Comment," Springfield Union, February 22, 1949; 12.
      - "Westinghouse Delegates Republican Reversed," Springfield Union, February 26, 1949; 13.
      - "Westinghouse Union Chief Hits at Indiscriminate Lay-offs and Cost Cutting," Springfield Union, April 8, 1949; 14.
      - "Westinghouse Shorter Week is Goal," Springfield Daily News, April 29, 1949; 15.
    - Local 202 Newspaper Clippings, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - "What's the Score?," Springfield Daily News, May 9, 1949; 1.
      - "UE's Leaflets Hit Hysteria Over Leaflet," Springfield Daily News, May 10, 1949; 2.
      - "UE Delegate Paid Own Way is Cimino Reply to Forsstrom," Springfield Union, May 11, 1949; 3.
      - "Prove UE Heads are Red, is Forsstrom's Challenge," Springfield Union, May 13, 1949; 4.
      - "600 Furloughs Reel Lowdown on Slowdown," Springfield Daily News, May 23, 1949; 5.
      - "Westinghouse Crew Told Pay out of Line Now," Springfield Daily News, May 27, 1949; 6.
      - Springfield Daily News, May 28, 1949; 7.
      - "Left Wing Sponsor for Matles Talk," Springfield Daily News, June 15, 1949; 8.
      - "Matles Rally Sponsor is Not UE Union Man," Springfield Daily News, June 16, 1949; 9.
      - "Contract Said to Bar Discussion Benefits Now," Springfield Daily News, June 16, 1949; 10.
      - "What Does Matles Direct," Springfield Union, June 16, 1949; 11.
      - "Unemployment UE Member Loses Right to Vote," Springfield Union, June 20, 1949; 12.
      - "Matles Chat is Explained by Mrs. Sutton," Springfield Union, June 21, 1949; 13.
      - "Holyoke UE Picks Holliday as it's Envoy," Springfield Union, July 11, 1949; 14.
      - "Westinghouse UE is Urged to Vote Right Wing," Springfield Union, July 11, 1949; 15.
      - "Left Wingers Losing Ground in UE Unions," Springfield Daily News, July 11, 1949; 16.
      - "Right Wingers in UE Achieve New Victory," Springfield Daily News, July 12, 1949; 17.
      - "Westinghouse Union Elect Right Wingers," Springfield Union, July 12, 1949; 18.
      - "UE Leader Branded, Praised in Hot Battle of Leaflets," Springfield Union, July 14, 1949; 19.
      - "Westinghouse Union Chiefs Ignore Claim," Springfield Daily News, September 27, 1949; 20.
      - "UE is Criminal of Clostand on Married Girls", 1949; 21.
      - "Married Women Again Issue at Westinghouse", 1949; 22.
  - Local 203
    - Local 203 Officers Lists, February 10, 1944-March 6, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Lists, February 10-August 5, 1944; 1-3.
      - List with January 23, 1947, Julius Emspak Letter to Louis Santoianni, January 3, 1947; 4.
      - Lists, April 23, 1947-March 6, 1950; 5-10.
    - Local 203 Incoming Correspondence, September 13, 1940-September 9, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - William Cahn to Josephine Willard Regarding Political Action and General Electric Strikes, February 15, 1946; 1.
      - Cahn to Willard, February 25, 1946; 2.
      - Cahn to Willard Regarding White Collar Workers and General Electric Strike, June 6, 1946; 3.
      - Cahn to Ellis Brooks Regarding UE News, May 31-June 1, 1949; 4-5.
      - Cahn to Brooks Regarding Publicity with Sample Letter to Editor, July 13, 1949; 6.
      - Cahn to Brooks Regarding Publicity, September 9, 1949; 7.
      - J.W. Coburn to P.J. Koons Regarding Women and Grievances, February 14, 1949; 8.
      - Josephine Dermody to Koons Regarding Wages, White Collar Workers and War Labor Board, September 30, 1944; 9.
      - Julius Emspak to John Doelling Regarding UE News, September 13, 1940-June 20, 1941; 10-14.
      - Emspak to Joseph Julianelle Regarding Staff Members, November 3, 1942; 15.
      - Emspak to Julianelle Regarding Local 203 General Electric Collective Bargaining, November 25, 1942; 16.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Julianelle Regarding General Electric Collective Bargaining, Productivity and Conscription, November 1, 1942; 17.
      - Emspak to Frank Fazekus Regarding Political Action, March 10, 1943; 18.
      - Emspak to Fazekus Regarding Speed-up and Safety with Mrs. Terry Brewster Letter to UE, August 28, 1943; 19.
    - Local 203 Incoming Correspondence, March 10, 1943-November 3, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Vicinanza Regarding Veterans and Finances, January 9, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to John Bucko Regarding Local 203 General Electric Strike, March 4, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Fred Bylcher Regarding Veterans and Finances, December 23, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak Telegram to Joseph Julianelle, April 16, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to John Bucko Regarding Finances, May 27-July 23, 1947; 5-6.
      - Emspak Telegram to Julianelle Regarding Finances, July 25, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Julianelle, August 19, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to Julianelle Regarding Finances, September 2, 1947; 9.
      - Emspak to Ellis Brooks Regarding Finances, January 13-February 3, 1948; 10-11.
      - Emspak to Reinier Bosch Regarding Finances, March 16, 1948; 12.
      - Emspak to Brooks Regarding UE News, May 27, 1949; 13.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Frank Fazekus Regarding Connecticut UE Legislative Conference, March 10, 1943; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Walter Clarke Regarding District Council Meeting, May 10, 1944; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to Terry Brewster, May 10, 1944; 16.
      - Fitzgerald's Secretary to Walter Clarke Regarding Membership Meeting, May 16, 1944; 17.
      - Ray Klausner to Philip Koons, June 20, 1944; 18.
      - Fitzgerald to Harry Peklowsky Regarding Local 203 Constitution, October 26, 1944; 19.
      - Fitzgerald to Blycher Regarding Political Action and Congress of Industrial Organizations, September 12, 1945; 20.
      - Fitzgerald to Blycher Regarding Dues, November 13, 1946; 21.
      - Fitzgerald to Harold Kollmannsperger, November 3, 1949; 22.
    - Local 203 Incoming Correspondence, August 15, 1939-September 28, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Leo Jandreau to Philip Koons Regarding Stewards, January 19, 1944; 1.
      - Jandreau to Koons Regarding Wages, Schenectady General Electric and War Labor Board, January 21, 1944; 2.
      - Jandreau to Frank Fazekas, June 2, 1943; 3.
      - Jandreau Telegram to Fazekas Regarding General Electric Collective Bargaining, July 19, 1943; 4.
      - Jandreau to Fazekus Regarding Seniority, September 23, 1943; 5.
      - Jandreau to Fazekus Regarding Contracts, December 14, 1943; 6.
      - James Matles to Joseph Julianelle Regarding Factionalism and Grievances Procedure, August 15, 1939; 7.
      - Matles to Julianelle Regarding War Manpower Commission, February 19, 1943; 8.
      - Matles to Frederick Blycher Regarding Local 203 General Electric Strike, January 30, 1946; 9.
      - Selma Kaslick to Frederick Mensch Regarding Local 203 Stewards Banquet, April 29, 1946; 10.
      - Stephen Rosner to Ellis Brooks Regarding Publicity, September 28, 1949; 11.
      - Benjamin Riskin to Jake Goldring, August 8, 1946; 12.
      - A.N. Towsen to Koons Regarding Wages and Schenectady and Fort Wayne General Electric, May 20, 1944; 13.
      - Joseph Turkowski to Koons Regarding Grievances, September 6, 1944; 14.
      - Turkowski Telegram to Koons Regarding Grievances, 15.
    - Local 203 Outgoing Correspondence, January 20, 1943-March 22, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Oliver Arsenault to Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, January 20, 1943; 1.
      - Dorothy Babey to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 24, 1947; 2.
      - Sigrid Billing to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Unemployment and Factionalism, March 22, 1949; 3.
      - Frederick Blycher to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, Grievances, General Electric Contract and War Labor Board, July 2, 1944; 4.
      - Blycher to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 1, 1945; 5.
      - Blycher to Joseph Dermody Regarding White Collar Workers, April 14, 1945; 6.
      - Blycher to Paul Seymour Regarding UE Officers, Constitution, and Finances, August 2, 1945; 7.
      - Blycher to Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action, August 28, 1945; 8.
      - Blycher Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Wages, November 16, 1945; 9.
      - Blycher to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 14, 1946; 10.
      - Blycher to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, October 15, 1946; 11.
      - Blycher to Fitzgerald Regarding Dues, November 12, 1946; 12.
      - Blycher to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 23, 1946; 13.
      - Blycher to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, December 17, 1946; 14.
    - Local 203 Outgoing Correspondence, February 11, 1943-September 16, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - Reinier Bosch to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 10, 1948; 1.
      - Terry Brewster to UE Regarding Speed-up and Safety, August 12, 1943; 2.
      - Brewster to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Grievances and Political Action, May 8, 1944; 3.
      - Ellis Brooks to UE Regarding Supplies, June 24, 1948; 4.
      - Brooks to William Cahn Regarding Publicity and Profits with Letter to Editor; September 15, 1944, Bridgeport Article "UE-CIO Proposes Vote on Strike Against General Electric"; and Bridgeport Article "Reinvestor", September 16, 1949; 5.
      - John Bucko to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 9, 1947; 6.
      - Walter Clarke to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meetings, May 15, 1944; 7.
      - Frank Fazekas to Emspak Regarding General Electric Contracts, Wages and Overtime with S.T. Powell 48-hour Working Schedule Notice, February 11, 1943; 8.
      - Fazekas to Emspak Regarding Connecticut UE Legislative Congress, March 4, 1943; 9.
      - Fazekas to Fitzgerald Regarding Connecticut UE Legislative Congress, March 4, 1943; 10.
      - Fazekas to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, May 14, 1943; 11.
      - Fazekas to Leo Jandreau Regarding Leave of Absence with General Electric Re-employment as New Employee Pledge, September 7, 1943; 12.
    - Local 203 Outgoing Correspondence, 1939-1944 (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Frank Fazekas to Julius Emspak Regarding Wages and Runaway Shops, September 25-October 4, 1943; 1-2.
      - Fazekas to Emspak Regarding Danbury General Electric, October 7, 1943; 3.
      - Fazekas to UE Regarding Local 203 Officers, December 27, 1943; 4.
      - H. Hoffner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Political Action, 1944; 5.
      - Joseph Julianelle to James Matles Regarding Boycotts, August 9, 1939; 6.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Job Classifications and General Electric Conference Board, August 27, 1942; 7.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Lunch Hours and General Electric Conference Board, August 27, 1942; 8.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Women, Wages and General Electric Conference Board, September 30, 1942; 9.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Hours, Organization and Overtime, October 7, 1942; 10.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, October 28, 1942; 11.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Apprentices and War Manpower Commission, November 19, 1942; 12.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Recreation and Political Action with "To Young Men of the Bridgeport Works" Leaflet and November 20, 1942, Bridgeport Work News Article "Head General Electric Youth's Club", November 24, 1942; 13.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Productivity, Conscription and General Electric Conference Board, November 27, 1942; 14.
      - Julianelle to Major W.H. Martell Regarding Guards and Military, December 5, 1942; 15.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Local 203 Officers with January 8, 1943, Matles Letter to Julianelle, December 22, 1942; 16.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Overtime, December 5, 1942; 17.
      - Julianelle to UE Regarding Address Change, January 2, 1943; 18.
      - Julianelle to Matles Regarding War Manpower Commission, February 12, 1943; 19.
    - Local 203 Outgoing Correspondence, September 2, 1943-March 7, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Joseph Julianelle Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 16, 1947; 1.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, August 18, 1947; 2.
      - Julianelle to Albert Fitzgerald, September 5, 1947; 3.
      - Julianelle Telegram to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, 4.
      - Julianelle to Emspak Regarding Staff Member, 5.
      - Harold Kollmannsperger to James Matles Regarding Unemployment and Local 203 Officers Elections, November 1, 1949; 6.
      - Philip Koons Telegram to Leo Jandreau Regarding Stewards, January 19, 1944; 7.
      - Koons to Jandreau Regarding Wages, Schenectady General Electric and Tool Makers, January 19, 1944; 8.
      - Koon to J.W. Coburn Regarding Women, February 12, 1944; 9.
      - Koon to Emspak Regarding Address Change, February 18, 1944; 10.
      - Koon to Joseph Dermody Regarding Wages, May 17, 1944; 11.
      - Koon to Fitzgerald Regarding Executive Order 9250, June 16, 1944; 12.
      - Koon to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Political Action, June 16, 1944; 13.
      - Koon to Joseph Turkowski Regarding White Collar Workers, September 7, 1944; 14.
      - Michael Marinaccio Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 203 Officers, December 17, 1947; 15.
      - Marinaccio to Maurice Reid Regarding Local 203 Officers, March 7, 1950; 16.
      - Frederick Mensch to UE Regarding Stewards Banquet, April 26, 1946; 17.
      - Andy Norvak to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, July 31, 1947; 18.
      - Harry Pelkowsky to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Political Action Committee, September 20, 1944; 19.
      - Pelkowsky to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Local 203 Constitutions, October 23, 1944; 20.
      - Peter Ross to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, September 2, 1943; 21.
      - Jo Willard to William Cahn Regarding General Electric Strikes with January 31, 1946, Cahn Letter to Willard, January 30, 1946; 22.
    - Local 203 Salary and Expense Letters, John Doelling, December 13, 1940-January 9, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Local 203 Notices of Deliquency and Suspension, August 1946-January 1948 (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Suspension with August 21, 1946, Julius Emspak Letter to Richard Linsley, August 1946; 1.
      - Suspension, October-November 1946; 2-3.
      - Delinquency, April 10-September 8, 1947; 4-7.
      - Suspension, September 15, 1947; 8.
      - Delinquency, October 6, 1947; 9.
      - Suspension with Emspak Letter to Albert Smith, October 22, 1947; 10.
      - Deliquency, October-November 1947; 11-13.
      - Suspension, November 14, 1947; 14.
      - Deliquency, November 21, 1947; 15.
      - Suspension with Emspak Letter to Smith, December 22, 1947; 16.
      - Delinquency, December 1947; 17.
      - Suspension with January 22, 1947, Emspak Letter to Joseph Caiazza, January 1948; 18.
    - Local 203 National Labor Relations Board Petitions, June 1944 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - Tool Designers Certification, June 26, 1944; 1.
      - Draftsmen Certification, June 1944; 2.
    - Local 203 Expulsions, February 6-November 16, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Joe Caiazza Local 203 Stewards Council Report to James Matles, February 6, 1947; 1.
      - Special District Council Meeting Minutes with Report and Recommendations of Appeals Committee of UE District 2, June 21, 1947; 2.
      - Joseph Julianelle to Julius Emspak, August 18, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Julianelle, September 2, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Albert Smith, September 15, 1947; 5.
      - Joseph Dermody Report to Local 203 Membership Meeting, November 16, 1947; 6.
    - Local 203 Expulsions, UE vs. Beresick Plantiff Memo, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Local 203 Bridgeport General Electric, Santionianni et al vs. UE et al, January 10-November 20, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Local 203 Bridgeport General Electric, Fitzgerald vs. Santoianni et al, April 10-March 31, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Local 203 Program, Correspondence, Lists, Statements and Proposals, June 17, 1942-July 24, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Suggestions on Operations of War Production Committees, June 17, 1942; 1.
      - Explanation of Agreement Regarding Local 203 General Electric Contract, 1942; 2.
      - J.W. Coburn Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Grievances, April 15, 1943; 3.
      - Organizational Program with Charles Rivers Letter to James Matles and "What Does GE Local 203 Mean to You?" Leaflet, September 1943; 4.
      - Rivers to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, May 12, 1944; 5.
      - Memo Regarding Women and Wages, 1944; 6.
      - Memo Regarding Wages and Job Classification, 1944; 7.
      - UE Convention Delegate List, September 1944; 8.
      - Joseph Dermody to Julius Emspak, July 19, 1946; 9.
      - Albert Smith to David Ratner Regarding Finances and 203 News, March 5, 1948; 10.
      - Berescik Statement, July 24, 1949; 11-12.
      - General Electric Collection of Union Dues Proposed Routine Draft, 13.
      - Mailing List, 14.
    - Local 203 Newspapers, 203 News, April 16, 1948-February 17, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Local 203 Leaflets, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Slate Card, 1944; 1.
      - "James Kelly" Regarding Local 203 Officers Elections, 1944; 2.